-[Caine]: Need some time to relax?
Well, today is your special day,
because we're going to
the Digital Circus Tropical getaway...
Resort.
This trip is just wild --
unlike anything else --
because you get special gifts
all to yourself!
-[Pomni]: Oh, God, what now?
-[Caine]: Relax!
Everything is going to be fine.
Bur first, let me introduce you
to these seven Pomnis!
Oh, my.
-[Pomni]: What?
-[Pomni Pendant 1]:
Time for some good ol' sunshine!
-[Pomni Pendant 2]:
[maniacal laughter]
[BOINK!] you!
[SPLAT!] you, [BONK!]
-[Pomni Pendant 3]: I feel like a leaf...
-[Pomni Pendant 4]: I need a drink.
-[Pomni Pendant 5]: Hey, guys.
I'm just normal Pomni.
-[Pomni Pendant 6]: [villainous laughter]
[SPLAT!] you, [CRASH!] -- again!
-[Caine]: New and so charming!
Five common, one rare!
And an extra one
that is super, uh, rare.
Random they come,
seven Pomnai to collect,
but six you see
as you inspect.
For, SHHH!!
Keep your voice down.
Please speak calmly.
For we d-d-don't t-t-talk
about THAT rare Pomni.
-[Pomni Pendant 7]:
Iconic catch phrase!
-[Pomni]: Are you going to be
rhyming for this whole thing?
-[Caine]: [flatly]
Yeah.
[whimsical]
Now, relax and sit back!
Patience is key!
And let's see what's behind
Curtain Number Th--
[stammers dispiritedly]
Yeah.
-[Pomni Pendant 1]: [yelps]
Why is he so heavy?
-[Pomni Pendant 6]:
Fat [CRASH]!
-[Jax]: [slurred, muffled]
-[Caine]: Tabarnak!
We can't have another death
at the resort!
Somebody do something!
Call a doctor!
-[Jax]: AAAAUUUGGHH--
-[Caine]: Or, yeah --
just do that, I guess.
Whatever.
-[Pomni]: Eh!
Who are those guys?
-[Caine]: Oh, those are
just resort guests.
Just ignore them, okay?
-[Ragatha Animiniz]:
This resort's just incredible!
I've never been so relaxed
in my whole life.
-[Zooble Animiniz]: Yeah.
Honestly, I gotta give it to Caine.
He's really outdone
himself with this.
-[Caine]: Hey, will you
shut the ffffffrick up?!
Uh-oh, it's Prize Number 2 time,
and what could it be?
Why, it's a funny,
squishy Kinger!
Hahaha, heeheehee!
-[Kinger]: [deep voice]
Hey, guys!
-[Pomni]: Why have all of these prizes
just been strange,
deformed versions of us?
It's a bit uncomfortable.
-[Caine]: Oh, uh --
Well -- Hmm.
[clicks tongue]
Would this make things better?
-[Kinger]: AAAAAAAAAAAAUUGHHH--
-[Pomni]: W-Why do you keep doing this?!
-[Pomni Animiniz]:
What's with all the negativity?
These prizes are incredible!
-[Kinger Animiniz]:
God, I wish that was me.
-[Caine]: Just shut the frig up!!
You no-talent,
mediocre piece--
For the first time ever,
we'll throw in this T--
-[Model]: Hey, guys.
-[Caine]: We'll throw in this, too!
A delightful little T-shirt
that'll be perfect for you!
-[Pomni]: Wait,
we've done T-shirts before --
[muffled scream]
-[Caine]: For the first time ever...
agai--
[chaos]
Turn your room into a museum
where anything goes
with these amazing prints
that will curl your toes!
-[Gangle Animiniz]:
Wow, this art looks so nice and pretty!
Made from artists with such
incredible talent and skill.
-[Caine]: [shrilly]
SHUT UP!!!!
Wha -- Are you kidding me?!
I'm in a meeting!!!!
Shut up!!!!
-[Pomni]: [weak exclamation]
-[Jax Animiniz]:
Boy, I could definitely use
one of those shirts
right about now.
Too bad we were
excluded from --
-[Caine]: SHUT --
Actually, wait a minute.
That gives me an idea!
Get in there, you freaks!
You, too!
-[Pomni]: [muffled]
I can't breathe!
-[Caine]: Wanna start your
tropical getaway today?
Then travel on over
to digitalcircus.store.
And now, until
the 27th of December,
you can save up to 30% off
on merch items store-wide!
Wowzers!
[sirens wailing]
Oh, no -- it's the 5-0!
They know about
the illegal shrimp show!
-[Officer]: We have the whole
place surrounded!
Come out with your hands up,
or you'll be grounded!
-[Caine]: Gotta go!
Be sure to remember --
this sale is only on
till the 27th of December!
[pounding on door]
Toodle-oo!
So, honest opinions, guys.
Whatcha think?
-[Fish 1]: [speaking Spanish throughout]
-[Fish 2]: Where's the
continental breakfast?
-[Fish 2]: Rhyming like a fool.
[muffled speech continues]
-[Caine]: [sighs]
This isn't fun anymore.
[both shrieking]
[festive music plays]
♪♪